

CHERNI MARWA

PL/SQL DEVELOPER

About Me

Highly Motivated IT Engineer with more than 2 years of experience in PL/SQL development, I'm mostly skilled in data management, including migration, integration, optimization, and ERP systems development.

- +216-55-181-802
- chernimarwa0000@gmail.com
- Tunis, Ben Arous El mourouj 4, Zurikh street
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/marwa -cherni-719112286/

LANGUAGE

- English
- French
- Arabic
- Japanese (Basic)
- Turkish (Basic)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

SQL, PL/SQL, PostGIS, PostgreSQL, SQL*Plus, SQL server, Oracle Forms & Reports, JasperReports, Oracle Apex, Toad, DBeaver, SQLdeveloper, StarUML, Gitlab, Fork, Agile: Scrum, JIRA, PHP, CSS, SprinBoot, Angular, NodeJS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TESSI - IT Services and IT Consulting
2022 - present Contract PL/SQL Developer

Data Analysis and Management: Analyzed customer needs to identify data requirements and optimize data management strategies.

PL/SQL Development: Designed and implemented stored procedures and functions using PL/SQL to enhance system performance and generate dynamic reports.

XML Expertise: Created CLOB data types with embedded XML for flexible insurance flow editing and reporting.

Project Management and Version Control: Effectively managed projects using Agile methodologies (Scrum) and tools like Jira and GitLab, including sprint reviews.

SIGA - **S**ystème **I**nformatique et **G**estion **A**utomatisée Automated Systems Management

2022 - present Full Time PL/SQL Developer

UML Design and Project Management,
Diagnosis of existing information systems,
Optimizing SQL Queries,

Javascript and PL/SQL scripting,

Developing and Deploying a three-tier architecture Web Applications with Oracle Apex, Oracle Forms,

Report Generation and Management with Oracle Reports and Jasper

EDUCATION

ISSAT Sousse

Software Engineering degree/ Master degree 2017-2020

FSEG Tunis

Applied Degree in IT Management -Bachelor degree 2014-2017

SIMAC - Société de l'Informatique de MAnagement et de Communication

IT Management and Communication Company 2021 - 2022 Full Time PL/SQL Developer

Providing functional and technical consulting services for the design and development of ERP systems across various modules: Financial Management, Human Resource Management (HRM), Electronic Document Management System (EDMS).

Developing and implementing PL/SQL programs for Data management, Report Generation and Testing. workshops to train and assist clients on system functionalities and best practices.

STEG - Société Tunisienne d'Electricité et du Gaz Electricity and Gas Company of Tunisia 2020 Internship

Design and Development of a STEG Network Digital Mapping Web Application Technical Environment: Spring Boot and Angular

Tunisie Télécom - Telecommunications of Tunisia 2018 Internship

Development of a web application for managing customer complaints using PHP scripting langage for backend and CSS for frontend

CTN - Compagnie Tunisienne de Navigation Tunisian Navigation Company 2017 Internship

Analysis, Design and Development of a Web Application for Withholding Tax Management within an Oracle environment: Oracle Forms.

This project involved a thorough initial study to understand the business requirements and user needs in order to design the application architecture, user interface, and functionalities